

# VICTOR CHIKWADO UDECHUKWU

Frontend Developer

# About Me

A computer science graduate with B.sc degree, internship and one year work experience in web development. Highly poised and dedicated with talent in design principles and programming languages. Excellent eye for visual aesthetics paired with insight into data and backend functionality. Strong work ethics, adaptability, and exceptional interpersonal skills. Adept at working effectively unsupervised and quickly mastering new skills.



+2349064514082



victorchikwado122@gmail.com



plot 10 2nd avenue mopol junction adamo ikorodu lagos

# LANGUAGE

English

# **EXPERTISE**

- Version Control Systems: Git, Github
- Website Analytics Tools
- Analytical Thinking
- JavaScript Libraries and Frameworks
- Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- Time Management and Prioritization
- User Experience Design
- Microsoft Office
- Project Management
- Creativity and Innovation
- Graphic and User Interface Design
- Technical Requirements Analysis
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Time Management and Prioritization
- Front-End: HTML5, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY and BOOTSTRAP.

# **EXPERIENCE**

NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (NIIT) LAGOS - NIGERIA JANUARY 2020 -JUNE 2022

#### **JOB DESCRIPTION:**

- LEARNING PYTHON LANGUAGE
- .TRAINING OF INTERNS AND STAFFS IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
- LEADING THE TEAM IN DEVELOPER A WEBSITE TO BUILD MORE MEDIA VISIBILITY

COLLEGE OF MEDICINE UNIVERSITY COLLEGE HOSPITAL, IBADAN OYO STATE. JANUARY 2023 -DECEMBER 2023

#### **JOB DESCRIPTION:**

- INCHARGE OF NETWORKING FOR THE SCHOOL"S SERVERS
- UPGRADE AND CONSTANT MAINTENANCE OF THE SCHOOL"S WEBSITE

# **EDUCATION**

## **BABCOCK UNIVERSITY.**

COMPUTER SCIENCE 2017 - 2022

#### APATA MEMORIAL HIGH SCHOOL

WEST AFRICAN EXAMINATION COUNCIL 2011 - 2017

# **LAUREL NURSERY AND PRIMARY SCHOOL**

2006 - 2011

## SKILLS SUMMARY

**Design Process** 

Project Management

89%